Nguồn: Nguyễn Thanh Lâm
Chúc các bạn xem phim vui vẻ!
We're all familiar
with the illegal poaching...
Of endangered animals
in the wild...
But never before has an animal in
captivity been slaughtered for its pelt.
Animal protection groups
that monitor the international trade...
In game contraband
have further told us...
That a white Siberian tiger
is so rare that the offer...
- Of a pelt would surely draw the
attention... -
Of law enforcement agencies.
Shortly before dawn this morning...
Security staff at London Zoo
discovered the excoriated carcass...
Of its prized three-year-old
female Siberian tiger, Sue Ling.
Police sources have suggested...
That the killing was contracted
by a private collector.
Oh, isn't that horrible?
Who'd do a thing like that?
If the battle to preserve
endangered species
has moved into the urban
zoological park...
We must ask ourselves if
any animal in the world is safe.
- - This is Tim
Ryan, reporting from London Zoo.
Another bad day
for the animal kingdom.
Oh, one day...
Very soon, Pongo,
I'm going to make a sale.
We're fast approaching
the point where I'm
gonna have to start
eating your table scraps.
Oh.
I was exaggerating.
Well, shall we?
It's not that bad.
It's very important
this meeting goes well.
You know how I am about meetings.
I tend to get a little, well, nervous.
When I get nervous, I say things, I do
things I shouldn't say, I shouldn't do.
And the next thing we know, freelancing.
He's got the best instincts
in the industry.
Since he was six, he's picked
the top-selling game every year.
Well?
What do you think?
Potentially good graphics,
reasonably entertaining premise...
The dog's well-conceived
and the environments are engaging.
But I'm not interested
in a game that has...
A chubby little dogcatcher
as the bad guy.
Even girls won't like this game.
- Sorry, mate. - Yeah, but wait,
wait, wait. Herbert, wait!
What if there were a better villain?
You know, someone you could really hate?
It's not hatred that's important.
It's a desire to annihilate.
Top of the morning
to ya, Ma'am.
Morning, Ma'am.
Morning, Miss De Vil's office.
Could you hold, please?
Yes, I'll be with you in a moment.
Thank you. Good morning,
Miss De Vil's office. Could you hold?
Good morning, Miss De Vil.
- Morning, Miss De Vil.
- Morning.
Morning, Ma'am.
Anita, darling.
Good morning, Cruella.
- What a charming dog.
- Thank you.
- Spots?
- Yes, she's dalmatian.
- Inspiration?
- Yes.
- Long hair or short?
- Short.
- Coarse or fine?
- I'm afraid it is a little coarse.
- Pity! - But it was very
fine when she was a puppy.
Redemption! We need to have
a little girl talk.
Come to my office.
Bring the drawing.
Now, darling, tell me
more about these spots.
I did leopard spots
in the '80s.
Well, dalmatian spots are
a little different, aren't they?
- Cozy. Classic.
- Cuddly. Less trashy.
Exactly!
Do you like spots, Frederick?
Oh, I don't believe so, Madame.
I thought we liked stripes this year.
What kind of sycophant are you?
Um, what kind of sycophant
would you like me to be'?
Frederick...
I'm beginning to see spots.
- What would it cost us to start again
on next year's line? - Millions.
- Can we afford it?
- Well, yes...
Pay it, darling. Now go away.
I have to talk to Anita.
Alonzo?
Did you ask Anita if
she'd like something to drink?
Oh, l-l... I'm fine, thank you.
Sit down, please.
How long have you been
working for me'?
Two years last August.
- And you've done wonderful
work in that time. - Thank you.
- I don't see you socially, do I?
- No.
And you're not very well-known,
despite your obvious talent.
Well, notoriety doesn't
mean very much to me.
Your work is fresh and clean,
unfettered, unpretentious.
It sells.
And one of these days...
My competitors are going
to suss out who you are...
And they're going
to try to steal you away.
Oh, no. If I left,
it wouldn't be for another job.
Oh, really?
What would it be for?
Well, I don't know.
Urn, if I met someone, if working here
didn't fit in with our plans.
- Marriage.
- Perhaps.
More good women have been
lost to marriage...
Than to war, famine,
disease and disaster.
You have talent, darling.
Don't squander it.
Well, I don't think that it's something
we have to worry about.
- I don't have any prospects.
- Thank God.
Well, I should be
getting back to work.
Yes, please do.
Alonzo.
The drawing.
Take the drawing from Anita
and hand it to me!
Is that difficult?
Thank you.
Now go. Stand somewhere 'til I need you.
I look wonderful in spots.
However, I would like
to make one small change.
We could do this in linen.
It would be stunning in fur.
But you'll be wearing it
to the Chesterton Trials.
That's in April.
Fur would be inappropriate.
But it's my only true love, darling.
I live for fur. I worship fur.
After all, is there a woman
in all this wretched world who doesn't?
Give it to Anita.
Oh.
It is rather amusing, isn't it?
What is?
Well, if we make this coat...
It would be as if
I were wearing your dog.
Woof! Woof!
[ Si9hi"91
Sorry, Pongo.
I didn't mean to take so long.
- If I could just sell a game, we might
be able to get a car. -
Come on.
" " P°"go!
Pongo!
Whoa!
Slow down!
- Slow down!
- Hey! Watch it!
Oh!
" P°llgo!
_ Hey!"
Whoa!
Pongo! Pongo! Pongo!
Aaah!
Ooh!
Pongo!
Turn!
Aaah!
- No, Pongo!
- Aaah!
- Stop! Stop! Ooh!
Ee-ee-ee-ee-ee!
,  " P°llgo!"
Pongo!
Whoa!
Aaah!
I don't think
he wanted to do that.
There we go, Perdy.
Oh, now stop it. Okay, go!
Go fetch it. Good girl!
Come on, bring it back.
Come here.
Yeah, good girl.
Okay. Oh, now, come on,
let's go again.
Pongo!
Go fetch the ball.
Goon
Hello.
Who are you?
Aaah!
L got you.
Very smart.
Very funny.
- Everybody had a good laugh.
- Let go of that dog!
- Stay outta this, lady.
- Stop it, or I'll... I'll hit you!
Today is not a good day
to threaten me, Ma'am.
I don't care if it's a good day
or a bad day, I'll hit you nonetheless!
- Whatever. - Okay, I gave you
a good and proper warning.
Look, I've had...
Now, release my dog...
Or I'll hit you again!
Your dog?
Yes, that is my dog.
Will you let her go?
Excuse me.
- He's a she.
- -
_  _
Hello, Pongo.
I, beg your pardon, Ma'am.
I'm sorry. My mistake.
- What do you got in that purse
of yours? Rocks? - Oh, no.
Bricks. I've been
paving my garden...
And every time I see a discarded brick,
I just pick it up.
- How many did you find today?
- Three.
- Three? Oh, well, that's what
I would've guessed. -
- Why are you all wet?
- I went swimming in the pond.
- Oh, you shouldn't have. The
water's filthy. -
Yes, and it tastes like fish.
And, urn, you've lost a shoe.
Did you know that?
Yes, I did.
As a matter of fact, I did.
- I noticed it running down the gravelled
path. - Oh, I'm ever so sorry.
I mean, you know, I
thought if you were silly
enough to go swimming
in a dirty pond...
You'd be silly enough
not to realize you'd lost a shoe.
Actually, I crashed
my bicycle in the pond.
And the only part of my body
that wasn't injured was my head.
But now, thanks to you, I got
the complete set of bodily injuries.
- Well, it was nice being assaulted
by you, Ms.... - Oh, my name's Anita.
- Anita?
- And yours is Roger.
- Urn, I read it on your dog's
identification tag. - Oh. Oh, yes.
Well, nice meeting you.
I hope I didn't alarm you.
Oh, no, that's fine since...
Well, we both seem to have
a certain fondness for dalmatians.
Yes.
_
Well, they certainly have...
- A certain fondness for each
other, don't they? - Yeah.
Well, Pongo...
Your roving eye's gotten me
in enough trouble for one day.
Why don't you come with me
and we'll go home?
Urn, are you sure you'll be all right?
Perhaps you should call your doctor.
I'll be fine, fine. Just...
Good luck with your bricks.
If you have a concussion,
you shouldn't be left alone, you know.
- Pongo, you could've gotten me killed,
you know that? -
You risk losing your master
for a brief frolic with a female?
Come on.
Jolly nice human, don't you think?
Fools aren't born, Pongo. Pretty girls
make them in their spare time.
Shall we?
Come on.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
J”J'
J5
You have it all wrong, Pongo. I'm simply
trying to decide on a route home.
It has nothing whatsoever to do with
Anita... if that's even what her name is.
J5
Perdy!
What is it?
Oh!
PongolPongo'.
Easy'. Easy'. Easy'.!
0h! Oh!
Perdy!
Stop! Look out!
Perdy, stop!
Perdy!
- Aaah!
- Look out!
Aaah!
Oh!
Oh, I've never
been rescued before.
It was very exciting. You were
ever so sweet to give me a kiss.
That wasn't a kiss.
That was mouth-to-mouth resuscitation.
- Oh.
- Besides, it... it didn't work very well.
You're supposed to lie
flat on your back and remain still.
I couldn't really do it properly
with your arms around my neck.
- I'm ever so sorry.
- No, no, no, that's quite all right.
Well, you give
a very good rescue.
Thank you.
Oh.
I think we have a problem.
I think my dog is in love.
I think mine is, too.
Why is that a problem?
They're going to be brokenhearted
when you leave.
Oh, I don't think I could bear to live
with a brokenhearted dalmatian.
Yes, they're miserable
when they're lonely.
- Well, we'd better think of something.
- I agree.
- Do you want another cup of marriage?
- Excuse me'?
Tea?
Another cup of tea?
- You said "marriage."
- Marriage?
Yes, that's what you said.
I... I mean, you meant to say "tea"...
But it...
it came out "marriage."
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you want another cup of tea?
I do.
You... You do?
I will.
You will?
If you ask me.
Would you?
Yes.
For as much
as Roger and Anita...
Have consented together
in holy wedlock...
And have witnessed the same
before God and this company...
And thereto have given and pledged
their troth either to other...
And declared the same...
By the giving
and receiving of a ring...
And by joining of hands...
I pronounce that they be
man and wife together.
In the name of the Father...
And of the Son
and of the Holy Ghost.
- Amen.
God the Father, God the Son...
God the Holy Ghost...
Bless, preserve and keep you.
The Lord, mercifully with
his favor, look upon you...
And so fill you with all
spiritual benediction and grace...
That ye may so live
together in this life...
And in the world to come.
And may you have
life everlasting.
- Amen.
Right. Now let me tell you a bit about
this bloke Skinner before we meet him.
Now supposedly,
when he was quite young...
This dog tore open
his throat...
And ripped out
his vocal cords...
Leaving him brutally scarred
and completely mute.
He cannot talk at all.
Now pay atten-
Look at me. Pay attention.
This is very important. There are
two things you must not do with Skinner.
Right? One:
Do not look at
the horrendous scar on his neck.
Two:
Don't talk to him.
- Understand? Not a word.
- Right.
Aaah!
Look at the size of that scar!
No bloody wonder
you can't talk, mate!
Excuse me just a minute, would you'?
Gol. Bloody gruesome line
of work you're in, Skinner.
The sight of all these deceased
creatures gives me a shrinky winky.
Much obliged, sunshine.
How could she do this to me?
- Morning, Ma'am.
- Sit!
- Tea?
- Please.
Please.
Thank you.
Ooh, oh, what
a beautiful day, Ma'am.
Blue skies, birds singing...
The laughter of school children
riding on the gentle breeze...
Get on with it, you imbecile!
Well, I...
I have here a present
from Mr. Skinner.
Oh.
Oh, it's magnificent.
Hello, my beauty.
Oh, come, come.
Come with me.
Come with me, my darling.
Let me see you.
Oh!
You were a big, bad boy,
weren't you, darling?
Yes, yes, yes.
Siberian tiger suits Madame
very well, indeed.
Mirror, mirror on the wall...
Who's the fairest of them all?
You are.
I remember you were
always very good at drawing...
When you were a little girl.
And now to be with you again
as you start a family of your own...
Is like a dream come true.
Oh, Nanny.
I don't think Roger and I are
quite ready to start a family yet.
Oh, that's a shame.
Aw, well, first the puppies.
Then the babies.
Puppies?
If I've done
my job right, Pongo...
When this new villain comes up, you're
gonna run from the room in a panic.
JJ"
J "J"
G" Ya!
A"sh!
- _
It's unmistakable, dear.
It's the look every woman gets when she
knows she's going to be a mother.
Notice how tranquil she is.
Her eyes are soft and warm.
Though you might not see it...
You can certainly feel
that she's smiling.
It's the smile we wear...
When we're guarding
a precious secret.
And now that she's living
for others as well as herself...
She's eating more.
And every now and again...
For no reason other than she's so happy
with herself, she sighs.
I think you're right, Nanny.
I think she does
look different.
- Oh, my goodness.
- What is it, Nanny?
Anita...
I think you're going
to have a puppy.
Oh!
Thank you so much.
- A month's time for a checkup, please?
- All right.
See you again soon, all right?
So?
Well, he said it's all great,
urn, the baby's nice and big...
- It's the right size.
- That's wonderful!
- Oh, no.
- What?
Cruella!
Anita, darling!
Oh, Anita.
Those dazzling dogs!
And you must be Rufus.
No, it's... it's Roger.
And it's a pleasure, Miss De Vil.
- What's a pleasure?
- Making your acquaintance.
Such a sweet thought.
I wish I could reciprocate.
Tell me, darling,
you married him for his dog.
Oh, darling,
I've missed you so.
I hate that you've taken leave.
But I'm still working.
Urn, you've been getting my sketches?
Well, it's not the same thing.
I miss the interaction...
And what is it that you do...
That allows you to support Anita
in such... splendor?
- I design video games.
- Video games?
Is he having me on'?
Oh, no, he's very good at it.
Urn, and it's a growing business.
Those horrible noisy things that
children play with on their televisions?
Someone designs them? What a senseless
thing to do with your life.
Oh, did Anita
tell you the news?
She's going to have a baby.
Is this true?
Yes.
Oh, you poor thing!
I'm so sorry.
We're very excited
about it, Cruella.
- You can't be serious.
- She is!
Well, what can I say?
Accidents will happen.
- We're having puppies, too!
- Puppies!
You have been a busy boy.
Well, I must say, that's somewhat
better news. I adore puppies!
- I'll expect a decline in your work
product. - Oh, I shouldn't think so.
Be sure to let me know
when the blessed event occurs.
Oh, well, it won't be
for another eight months.
The puppies, darling.
Ooh.
I've no use for babies.
Cheerio!
Cheerio, darling!
If I'm this nervous
about your puppies...
What am I gonna be like
when my baby arrives?
How can you be so calm?
Nanny!
Oh, my goodness!
Oh! Oh!
Gangway!
Is it time?
Ls there something I can do?
Maybe... Maybe I can be
of some help!
All right, get out,
peek in through the window...
And see if those puppies
have come yet.
Can I borrow your umbrella?
Be careful when you open it.
They're here!
The puppies are here!
You're a father, Pongo!
_  Tw u _ Two! o.
You're a father twice!
Make that three!
Three! Three, Pongo!
- Oh, my goodness! Four!
- Four!
Fifteen.
Did you hear that, boy?
Fifteen puppies!
Fourteen.
We lost one.
I'm sorry, Pongo.
I'm so sorry.
I wonder.
_
Fifteen!
We have 15 puppies!
Look. Oh!
Goodness gracious!
It's a miracle!
Anita, 15!
Fifteen again!
Oh!
We must call
this one "Lucky."
Look!
Look at him.
Oh.
- How's Perdy?
- She's tired.
Oh, bringing 15 puppies into the world,
I guess she's got a right.
Yeah. But they're
so beautiful.
You can
go in now, Pongo.
Here we are, Perdy.
Yes, it's Lucky.
Now make room, you others.
Well done, Perdy.
There's a good girl.
I'll leave you two alone.
I'm glad I'm only
having the one.
Anita?
There you are!
Where are the puppies?
They should have arrived by now.
How marvelous.
How marvelous!
How perfect...
Oh, the devil take it! They're mongrels!
No spots!
No spots at all!
What horrible little white rats!
Oh, but their spots
don't come 'til later.
- You're sure?
- Yes.
All right, put them in a bag.
I'll take them with me now.
- What? They were just born!
- I can see that!
But, Cruella, the puppies have to be
with their mother for several weeks.
- They're not ready to leave. - Fine, put
the little brutes on reserve for me.
- How much would you like?
- They're not for sale.
Oh'? You've come into
some money, have you'?
Did you design some silly game...
That will drive the delinquent kiddies
into frenzies of video delight?
- As a matter of fact, I have...
- No, no, what Roger means to say...
- Is that we're not sure
we're going to sell
the puppies.
- Anita, don't be ridiculous!
You can't possibly afford to keep them.
I'll pay you twice
what they're worth.
Come now, I'm being
more than generous. £500!
- On!
- £7,500!
Fair? £2 per spot.
But, Cruella,
what would you do with 15 puppies?
But that's irrelevant, Anita. She can't
have any because they're not for sale!
I'm getting very
tired of you, Roland!
- Roger!
- Whatever. Take it.
Take it.
Take it!
Cruella...
The puppies are not for sale.
You're quite... sure?
- Yes.
All right, keep the little beasts.
Do what you like with them.
Drown them, for all I care!
You're a fool, Anita!
I've no use for fools.
You're fired!
You're finished!
You'll never work in fashion again!
I'm through with all of you!
I'll get even!
Just wait!
You'll be sorry, you fools!
You idiots!
- Good evening, Madame.
- Out of my way!
JJ"
Hello, Pongo.
♪ Everybody I
♪ Everybody wants to be a cat ♪
Come on, you two,
let's go home.
Thank you, Pongo.
They're here! I've got them!
Anita, Roger.
I'm in the living room.
Now come on down and have a look.
Oh, you as well.
You heard that, did you?
Wait 'til you see what I've got
for you in this bag. Ha!
♪ Chestnuts roasting
on the open fire ♪
Jewel, look.
♪ Jack Frost nipping at your nose ♪
Let me put this on you. Oh.
♪ Yuletide carols
being sung by a choir ♪
Dipstick?
Come on.
That a boy.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Fidget?
Here.
♪ Tiny tots
with their eyes all aglow ♪
Two-tone?
- - I know. No, I
know. You all like to do it.
Come on, there we go,
there we go, there we go.
- [ Si9hi"91
- Wizzer.
Right, we're on.
Get...
Get your own!
Somebody didn't
finish their supper.
We're on a budget.
"Waste not, want not,"
that's my motto.
Who on earth?
Corning.
Corning!
- Good evening, Madame.
- Oh, my goodness!
- It's all right, lady. We're
professionals. -
Aaah!
Come here!
- Get her off!
- Time to go now!
- Let go of me!
- Straight ahead. Straight ahead.
- Police, help! Police, help!
- Push! Push!
- Get in there!
- Fingers!
Let me out of here!
Let me out!
- Open the door!
- Oh, do shut up!
Open the door!
Police!
Police! I'll see you
go to prison for this...
If it's the last thing I do.
There.
Well, the old bird
put up a good fight.
I like a bit of spirit in the woman.
That's all right for you to say.
You didn't get smashed in the face.
Shh, shh, shh.
Aw!
Give me the bag.
Come on, come on.
Here.
All right, come here, you...
Spotty little... dog!
Evening, General.
Montgomery! Heel, boy!
Heel, boy! Heel!
- Jasper...
- Stop it now!
- Do you know what I think?
- What's that?
I think that bulldog
knows what we just done.
Nah, it's a dog, Horace.
Dog's ain't got the brains
to figure things out.
Come on. At ease!
Luckily.
Come on home, Montgomery!
- I mean, I think... Pongo!
- Perdy!
Help! Police!
Where are they?
Oh, no!
They've taken the puppies.
Anita! Roger!
Thank God they're home!
Oh, thank goodness you've come.
- Why? What is it?
- The puppies.
Two men, they've stolen the puppies.
I tried to stop them.
They locked me in the cupboard.
I shouted and shouted,
but nobody came.
Good evening, Madame.
I sincerely hope
I've not disturbed your relaxation...
- But I have some good news.
- Did you get the puppies?
Affirmative.
All of them?
Every single one.
My faith in your limited intelligence
is momentarily restored.
Oh! You are
too kind, Madame.
They've got the 15!
Add them to the other puppies
we've already stolen...
And I have my cozy puppy coat.
I'll be wearing Anita's dogs.
- _
Right, well, I'm gonna fill me snoot
and go to bed. I'm dead tired.
I'm hearing dogs again, Jasper.
Oh, shut up in there!
- You keep your chin up. We'll do
our best. - Thank you, Inspector.
- Good night, Madame.
- Good night.
He was most sympathetic.
He says they're going
to do the best they can.
For what that's worth.
- Do you think they'll find them? - How are
they going to find 15 little puppies...
In a city this size?
If they're even in the city.
What can the police do?
What can we do?
What can anyone do?
Woof! Woof! Woof!
_  _
[ Weighing 1
Pongo!
- Did you hear that?
- What?
That noise.
- What noise?
- That noise I just heard.
- Did you hear it?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah. It sounded just like a complete
berk asking me irritating questions.
Oh, good, it's stopped now.
I'll be honest with you, mate.
This job is fast
losing its charm.
The housing stinks;
the food's lousy...
The lavatory facilities are appalling...
And so far, we haven't been paid
so much as one quid.
Oh, will you stop moaning!
Look, this time tomorrow night,
it's all over.
We get our boodle, we'll be out of here
before you can say, "Dead puppies."
' ,  Now, go to sleep
[ Sniffs 1
_  _
Mr. Skinner, suspicions are mounting.
Police are everywhere.
I want the job done tonight.
Can you do it?
Any way you want.
Poison them. Drown them.
Bash them on the head!
Got any chloroform?
I don't care how you kill the little
beasts. Just do it and do it now!
Pongo and Perdy
will turn up, won't they?
If you ask me, they will. I think
they just went looking for the puppies.
You know who did this,
don't you?
I, for one, wouldn't be
the least bit surprised.
She has a horrible temper on her.
The dogs never cared for her.
Dogs have a sixth sense
about things like that.
They can smell ill intentions.
Roger,
- What? What's wrong?
- Nanny, what did I do with my portfolio?
It's in the nursery closet, dear.
Anita?
She did steal the puppies,
and this is why.
She's going to
kill the puppies.
Right, that's it. Time to let
the little yappers have it.
We ain't supposed to do it.
That's Skinner's job.
Well, Skinner isn't here, is he?
Besides, I don't see why that
little runt should have all the fun.
How'd you wanna do it?
Well, personally,
I think I favor the fire iron.
Why, that...
that'll be Miss De Vil.
Fix your shirt
and tart up your hair.
Good eve... ning.
Hello?
Anybody there?
Maybe we was hearing things.
Oi!
- Get out of my truck!
- Yeah!
Go on! Get outta here!
Yeah!
There's plenty more where that came
from, should you elect to come back.
I don't believe it.
- _
I don't care what you say.
We bloody well
better be careful.
Yeah, that's right.
What we better be careful of...
Is the huge, thundering macroeconomic
bulk of your stupidity.
I ain't takin'
any more lip from you, mate.
Oh, forget about that. We have got
99 stinking puppies to find and kill.
Now get on with it!
Here, puppies.
PUP, PUP, Pup, pup, puppies.
Come here,
you speckled lap rat.
Snifﬂes
Stay.
You bug...
You come here!
I'm gonna get you, you little...
Cold.
Good evening, madame.
Good evening.
Hello.
What are you doing up there?
I'm... I was... I was just
fetching the puppies, ma'am.
And where... are...
the puppies?
Oh! There.
You see, once again...
Madame has, like a laser, gone straight
to the heart of the issue.
It's a quality
I've always admired in her.
"Where are the puppies?
Where are the puppies?" Brilliant.
Let me just say right now...
That I'm not...
absolutely a hundred percent certain...
Where the puppies are.
But if you'll just give me a second,
I'll check with my associate.
Horace?
Get down from there
and catch those puppies!
Hopelessly stupid, pathetic fools.
I'll find the bloody mongrels myself.
- - You just had to let
those puppies get away, didn't you?
- Never paying attention.
- Well, where was you?
Where wa... I was not
splashing about in the pond!
You've infuriated the old bag.
And if we don't get those puppies back,
then it's quite literally our heads!
Oh, come on!
- - Right. You
better get out and check the tailpipe.
We've got a condensation problem.
One of these days...
I'm gonna be full-up of you.
Aah!
Ooh.
Oh, do come on!
There! You see?
Turn the heater on, will ya?
No. Not with this thing
acting the way she is.
I don't want to risk losing power.
I can't stand the cold no more.
I want heat!
- Oh! No!
- Fire!
Too hot! Too hot!
Aah! Too hot!
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Aah!
Suspect apprehended...
Your suspicions were justified.
According to the staff, Miss De Vil left
earlier for a family property in Suffolk.
I have informed
the local police.
Officers there will be
on the lookout for your puppies...
AndMissDeViL.
I only hope we're not too late.
Oh!
This is extraordinary.
I'm reduced to tramping
through sewage...
Because my two imbeciles can't
keep track of a bunch of infant dogs!
Oh!
I do not believe it.
We got no truck, no dogs.
We are so dead.
Number 1 Dead Street, that's us.
Look! Tracks.
I love you.
There you are. You see?
If dogs are so smart, they wouldn't leave
tracks for wary predators such as us.
- Yeah. - Now, I've always said that
human beings are essentially superior...
You know, blessed with faculties of speech
and thought and a couple of other things.
Don't worry, I won't ruin
your little puppy coat.
I'm just going to make a few buttonholes.
Where are you, you filthy beast?
Oh, yes.
I love the smell
of near extinction.
Got it!
Oh! Oh-oh! Oh! Oh!
Stupidity, you see? That's your problem.
That's what's been holding you back.
If it was up to you,
you'd have taken hold of that wire...
Set fire to your undershorts,
cooked your tongue...
Before even thinking
it was electrified.
Point taken.
But what are the logs for?
"What are the..."
You see, the...
We stand upon the logs
and hop over...
Thereby avoiding painful electric shock.
Brilliant.
Right. Mount the log.
Extend leg.
All right.
Now, when I count to three, we jump.
- Ready?
- Yes.
One.
Aah!
Useless, disgusting creatures.
I'm sick to think
we breathe the same air.
Bingo!
Poor little things.
I'm gonna cut you off...
Then cut you up.
Darling, red isn't your color.
Give me the hat.
Give me the hat...
Or you'll become a hat.
Give it to me!
Oh!
Thank the Lord.
We're saved.
- Here you go.
- Up you go.
- Much obliged. Thanks.
- Watch your heads.
- Very kind.
- Thank you.
Nice and quiet.
- This is lovely. Yeah.
- Isn't it?
Nice and warm.
No animals neither.
You... beasts!
But I'm not beaten yet.
You've won the battle,
but I'm about to win the wardrobe.
My spotty puppy coat is
in plain sight and leaving tracks.
In a moment I'll have
what I came for, while
all of you will end
up as sausage meat...
Alone on some sad plastic plate...
Dead and medium red;
no friends, no family, no pulse...
Just slapped between two buns,
smothered in onions...
With fries on the side.
- Cruella De Vil has the last
laugh!  -
Miss De V“?
- Yes?
- We have a warrant for your arrest.
Oh'? Ls there
something wrong?
Stop. What's that up ahead?
Well, will you look at that.
Excuse me, madame.
Would you mind standing back?
I've come up with 98 pups.
The two adults make it 100 even.
We've got 100 here, sir.
Make that...
101 dalmatians, sir.
Congratulations.
You've just won
gold, silver and bronze...
In the Morons Olympics.
- Who won the gold?
- Shut up!
My business,
my reputation, my life...
Has been ruined
because you three incompetent twits...
Let yourselves be outsmarted
by a bunch of dumb animals!
And you call
yourselves men. Ha!
I've seen more intelligent
pieces of carpet!
Oh, they're here!
Anita!
Roger!
- The puppies!
- Here... Oh, my goodness! Look at them.
- 0h;
_ oh:
Oh:
Oh! That a boy!
That a boy! Yeah!
- That a boy!
- Oh! Oh!
Oh, thank you, Officer!
How can we ever repay you?
Well, your dogs were the only ones
with identification tags.
We have no idea
which puppy goes where.
Our records indicate
that so far...
Nobody has called
to claim the other puppies.
Now, they need a home, or...
Well, they go to the pound.
Oh, no. No.
No, no, no, no.
- Roger, we can't... We don't have room.
- Well, we'll get a bigger place.
We have 17 as it is.
What's a few more?
We'll work something out.
' ' [ Laughs 1
Oh.
You'll have dozens
of children, you know.
Well, I won't have them
chewing up the carpets...
Barking until all hours of the night.
All right.
Everyone inside before we all get cold.
Unload the puppies!
Get ready.
Cool!
Excellent villain, mate.
Thanks, Herbert!
- Congratulations.
- Why, yes. Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you... - See you in
my office. We've got terms to sort out.
- Okay. Great.
- Excellent villain, mate.
I don't be...
I can barely believe it.
Our baby is a year old.
- We have a new house, a new life...
- And we have each other.
We have Nanny.
- And I have the three of you.
- We have two wonderful dogs.
And they have their children.
And their stepchildren.
And their stepchildren
have children.
And their children
And speaking of children...
Roger, darling,
I've got the most wonderful news.
♪ Cruella De Vil ♪
♪ If she doesn't scare you
no evil thing will ♪
♪ To see her is to take a sudden chill ♪
♪ Cruella Cruella De Vil ♪
♪ Cruella, her lips ♪
♪ The ice in her stare ♪
♪ All innocent children
had better beware ♪
♪ She's like a spider
waiting for the kill ♪
♪ Look out for Cruella De Vil ♪
♪ At first, you'd think
Cruella is a devil ♪
♪ After time has worn away the shock ♪
♪ You come to realize ♪
♪ You seen her kind of eyes ♪
♪ Watching you from underneath a rock ♪
♪ This vampire bat ♪
♪ This inhuman beast ♪
♪ She oughta be locked up ♪
♪ And never released ♪
♪ The world was such a wholesome place ♪
♪ Until Cruella
Cruella De Vil ♪
♪ Cruella De Vil ♪
♪ If she doesn't scare you
no evil thing will ♪
♪ To see her is to take a sudden chill ♪
♪ Cruella ♪
Joe VilJ“
♪ Cruella, her lips ♪
♪ The ice in her stare ♪
♪ All innocent children
had better beware ♪
♪ She's like a spider
waiting for the kill ♪
♪ Look out for Cruella De Vil ♪
♪ At first, you'd think
Cruella is a devil ♪
♪ After time has wore away the shock ♪
♪ You come to realize
you've seen her kind of eyes ♪
♪ Watching you from under a rock ♪
♪ This vampire bat ♪
♪ Inhuman beast ♪
♪ Oughta be locked up never released ♪
♪ This world was such
a wholesome place until ♪
♪ Cruella De Vil ♪
♪ At first, you think
Cruella is a devil ♪
♪ After time has wore away the shock ♪
♪ You come to realize ♪
♪ You seen her kind of eyes ♪
♪ Watching you from under a rock ♪
♪ This world was such
a wholesome place until ♪
♪ Cruella De Vil ♪
♪ So evil even her hair's two-faced ♪
♪ Ain't like nothin' you ever seen ♪
♪ She's the dean of mean ♪
♪ Weed to message she's got
some doggone had intentions J J
I mean, let's face it. A person like her
could really ruin your whole day.